♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
(SCREECHING)
But I can’t speak any louder--
I’m in a library now.
What’s a library, Jeremie?
A data bank where
everything’s printed on paper.
And where you can’t make any noise!
Oh, I guess because you need silence
to concentrate on what you’re studying.
Yes, and so as not to miss the match point!
Hey, quiet!
Ye-a-a-a-a-ah!
Game set and match!
Yeah!
Ulrich!
Is that what you call studying?
In case no one told you,
this is not the school yard!
You are here to work, okay!
And work means silence!
And no more games from now on!
Ah! Okay, well, if that’s the
way you want to play,
I can play just as hard
as you can, my little friends!
Y-o-o-o-o-u!
Two hours detention!
I'm--!
Sorry about that, sir, I uh…
Hello there, Jeremie.
Would you come to my office now?
I want to talk to you. It’s very important.
Jeremie?
What’s going on?
Well, you know the principal.
He went on and on.
He says the school psychologist
has been observing me for a long time,
and he thinks that I’m an…
overly-gifted student.
Is that all? But that’s nothing!
We were scared that the principal
had found out about the lab! Big deal!
It’s worse than you think, Odd.
The shrinks decided that I have to
take all kinds of tests tonight
to determine what my IQ is.
Yeah, so?
If the tests show that
I have a really high IQ,
the guy is gonna see to it
that I get sent to another school.
Oh, no!
Are you saying that he’s gonna send you
to a school for like future Einsteins?
Yeah.
That is serious.
If you’re not here,
we can never go to Lyoko again,
and XANA will be able
to do what he wants.
It’s not just that, guys.
I don’t want to leave here
because of you all.
You’re my friends.
Hold on, cool it.
Don’t panic, okay?
I mean, they can’t
force you to change schools.
It’s not all that easy.
The psychologist creep
couldn’t wait to talk to my parents.
He told them that at that kind of school,
I’d be entitled to a big scholarship.
My folks aren’t gonna pass up
a great chance like that.
(RINGING)
What’s the big problem?
You mess up on the test,
and they’ll think you’re a total moron.
Nobody will ever know,
and you’re home free.
Sure, I thought of that.
Only there’s a problem
because tests like that
are full of all kinds of
trick questions,
and if you really want to
mess up and make mistakes,
you’ve got to be very clever.
But that’s great since
you’re the cleverest kid around!
Well, okay.
I’ll do my best to flunk.
But I can’t promise anything.
Uh, I’ll see you guys later.
Keep me posted, okay?
Ah, hello there, Jeremie.
Do you recognize me?
I’m Mister Simone,
the school psychologist.
Of course I do!
Is it really true that you’re
planning to get me transferred
to a school for gifted children?
That’s great! My parents
are gonna be so glad!
Well, that’s what we’re
here tonight to find out.
Now, to start off, I’m going to
give you a multiple choice test.
It’s a test in which you…
oh, I’m sorry, I’m sure
you already know.
Me? No.
Oh.
So, what’s for dinner?
Oh, I don’t know. Some kind of hash.
They all taste the same.
(SCREAMS)
Oh, no, it can’t be!
My brand-new Guuki dress!
I don’t believe it!
Ah! So you’re the savage that did this!
(SQUEALS)
Here, take that!
(PULSING)
Jeremie!
Jeremie, listen!
XANA’s woken up.
He must be preparing an attack.
Jeremie?
Sir, don’t you think we ought to stop?
But that would be silly, huh?
The tests are almost finished.
Besides, the lights are
bound to come on again.
Ah.
Oh, what kind of a
two-bit school is this?
(SQUEAKING)
Huh?
(SCREECHING)
Help!
That’s enough!
Get back to your seats
right now and quiet down!
Go on, now! The lights will
come on again soon.
Now stop all your
clowning around, understand?
Come on, now!
Shh!
Quiet down! Listen!
(SQUEAKING)
What?
Gaaah!
We’d better get out of here.
Uh…don’t panic!
Take that! And that!
Move, move! Go!
Don’t panic, I said!
Just get out of my way!
Oh, no.
Uh-oh.
We’re trapped.
Nice going, XANA.
The rats all waited for night time.
And they attacked us as soon as
we were all in the cafeteria.
(RINGING)
Is that you, Ulrich?
Huh? What?
(RINGING)
Oh, but…
After the test, you can make
all the calls you want.
Oh, what’s the matter!
Why doesn’t he answer?
The extinguishers, Jim! Hurry up!
Don’t panic!
J-Just don’t p-p-panic, okay!
Pass them down!
Okay, outside, everyone!
There are way too many of them!
We’ll never be able
to hold them back all night!
Help! Help!
Over here!
Sissi?
What’s she doing here, anyway?
We have to help her,
or she’s gonna be eaten alive!
That noise is unbearable.
Listen, this racket has got to--
Daaah!
Aaah!
They’re--they’re rats!
Like a whole army of them!
XANA.
They’re trying to eat through the door.
We’ve got to barricade it.
Ah, here she comes!
Your carriage, cinderella.
Welcome to the rat pack!
Okay, keep going alone, sir.
Let’s hope this will
hold them back long enough.
Aelita?
XANA has activated a tower, Jeremie.
I’ve spotted where it is.
I’m on my way there now.
I’ll try and get a closer look, okay?
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hello, Jeremie.
Yes, the rats have attacked.
Okay, right. We’ll meet at the lab.
We have to find a safe place.
Where, huh? The rats are all over.
I know one! The only place with no access
to the sewers is the science building.
Let’s go!
Better hurry.
Oh, this time we’re the rats in a trap,
and I don’t like it at all.
Hey, get a move on, huh?
The extinguishers are nearly empty!
Come on. Easy does it.
Faster!
Hurry up! Move!
Oh, what do I do now?
Okay, let’s go up to the roof.
If the rats get in,
we’ll be safe up there.
We have to get to the factory.
Jeremie will meet us there.
As soon as he can, that is.
Sounds great,
but how do we get there, huh?
Here I go.
Yeah!
Hey, wait! Come back!
What are you doing!
No, come back!
Hey, come back here! Hey!
Too late!
No choice.
We have to go over the wall.
Not rats. Anything but rats.
W-When I was a boy,
a rat came up to my…my room.
Bingo.
You stay here, sir.
I got to get to the photo lab.
Be right back!
XANA’s thought of everything.
Come on.
Care for a little cruise?
(SCREECHING)
Faster!
Hurry up! Faster! Hurry!
It worked! Great!
If they come, use this.
It’ll chase them away.
Stay! P-Please don’t go!
I’m afraid of rats!
Oh, no.
Hey, Jeremie. I’m in the lab.
I have to contact Aelita
and virtualize Odd and Ulrich.
Explain to me how to do it.
Listen up, now.
Okay, that’s done.
I found the activated tower,
and I’ve located Aelita.
She’s got a problem.
What?
Speak louder!
I can hardly hear you!
I have to type in the coordinates?
Say that again.
19 degrees west?
That’s it, isn’t it?
Wait, no. I said 79 degrees west!
79 degrees west!
Listen, Yumi, the rats have
invaded the city, do you hear?
Okay, then. I’m ready.
Yumi, can you hear me?
Transfer Odd.
Transfer Ulrich.
Scanner Odd.
Scanner Ulrich.
Virtualization.
It’s okay. You did it, Yumi.
Do you see Aelita?
No. She should be
around here somewhere.
Oh, no. I didn’t enter
the right coordinates!
I virtualized you too far
away from Aelita!
That’s okay. We could use
a little exercise to get warmed up.
Smile!
Do you see her now?
Yeah, I see her.
She’s here.
The only problem is she’s not alone.
Be careful.
Hello, princess.
That was close.
I just managed to get away.
Your two knights in armor
have come to protect you.
Hey, you know, this is kinda weird.
Odd, Ulrich, what is happening?
That’s a good question.
I don’t understand…
It could’ve been my mistake, although…
It’s XANA.
He’s changing the slope of the plateau.
Better hang on tight!
(YELLING)
Wow! Well done, Aelita!
Two krabs, a battery of lasers,
10 life points lost per impact.
Ulrich, cover Aelita.
She’s lost too many life points.
I’ll try to attract their attention.
Laser arrow!
No, Odd!
Get out of there now!
Odd! No!
Need any help?
Oh, Jeremie. You’re finally here.
Listen, Odd has just been devirtualized,
and Ulrich has hardly any life points left.
Well, you know what
you gotta do now, Yumi.
No!
Go on, Aelita.
You’re there now. Go on.
Say…say cheese.
Return to the past now.
Jeremie, hey, did you figure out
a way to flunk the test, hm?
Well, now that I know
all the questions,
I shouldn’t have any trouble
giving all the wrong answers.
Are you sure it’s gonna work?
Anyway, I’ve got a
foolproof way of flunking.
I’m gonna get all of
my answers from Odd.
Yeah, yeah.
Go on, laugh your heads off.
But who knows?
You might be in for a big surprise!
Quiet!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO